Applause for that channel.
Can you tell me what you want to talk to me about today, what's bothering you?
Yes!
No!
I can't believe I'm still saying this.
And the world to come
I want you to sing me a song.
Fashionable.
So, who wants to teach me?
Yes, please.
Hiyori, you're about to speak up.
I have a lot of quirks in my hair.
How can I make my hair smooth and silky like yours?
Well, it's beautiful, but...
My mom sprayed it really hard today, so it's fine.
Normally, my hair is very shaggy.
Hiyori, you know...
Let's eat wakame first!
I've eaten a lot of wakame since I was a little girl.
They laughed at me so much.
And when you grow up, go to a hair salon and get some straightening products.
How's it going? Did you solve it?
Yes, I solved it.
Really?
Do you like wakame? Can you eat wakame?
I love wakame.
Well, then, good for you. It's good for your hair.
Do you have any likes or dislikes?
I don't have any likes or dislikes.
No likes and dislikes.
No.
Wow. Green onions? I can't eat those.
I can eat a lot of green onions, as long as they're small.
Oh, wow, little green onions?
Yes.
Wow, wow. Do you guys have any likes or dislikes?Wow, wow, do you guys have likes and dislikes?
Yes, I do.
Yes? What?
Tomatoes.
Tomatoes? You don't have to eat those.
You don't have to eat that stuff.
No? You and your wife?
Yes.
Yes? What?
Green onions.
I can't eat leeks forever.
I can't eat them either.
You don't have to eat it?
You don't have to eat them.
There's nothing nutritious about them.
They look like hair.
But they're in every dish.
They're making a hell of a main street.
You might have a little trouble down the road... if you can't eat them.
That little guy in the back.
That's why I can't see his name.
Takeyagi, do you have any dislikes?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ah, ah, ah..,
That's what I mean.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I don't have that.
Then, let's call it Yu-chan's karuta
Yes, sir
Okay, please draw a card.
This one?
Yes, that way.
Ho!
So, please think of a Ho-karuta.
Oh, wait, what should we do with all those?Oh, wait, what am I going to do with all that stuff?
What do you mean, "a lot"?
I can think of a lot of words.
What's karuta?
Like "Oni ni Kanabou"?
It's a proverb.
What kind of things do you draw?
I draw good proverbs.
It looks like a proverb.
It means something good.
Emphasis.
Yes, I've got it. What is this karuta then?
Well, then, Ho.
Pearls for Homare.
Pearls for pigs?
Yes.
If you put a pearl in the hand of someone as great as Sawa Homare...
Sawa Homare is still amazing.
I mean, even with pearls, a great person is still a great person.
It means that he's so great that it's overshadowed.
That's what "pearls for pigs" means!
Pearls on a pig probably means...
What?
So giving pearls to a pig doesn't mean anything?
They don't know the value.
Because a pig is too much of a pig?
You're saying that giving pearls to a pig is worthless.
The opposite! I misinterpreted it a bit.
Pearls for Homare
Pearls that shine as bright as pearls
It's as good as a pearl.
What do you think it means to give a pearl to a pig?
It means that if you give a pearl to a pig...
A pig is so piggy that the pearls are a blur.
Strong.
When you said "ho," did you immediately say "homare"?When you got a "ho" did you immediately get a "homare"?
When I got a "ho," I also got a "homare" and a "hoshan.
I got a lot of things.
I wrote a respect comment.
I like social life.
I think it's Honda, isn't it?
I've been saying "Honda" a lot lately.
It's like Honda harassment.
I mean it in a positive way.
I mean it in a good way, but the way I cut it off... it's like I'm making fun of it.
They probably don't like me.
I'm not going to show it anymore.
I'm going to ask you to make a clay work that represents an English word.
This time, the word is perfect.
Perfect. It's hard.
Why is it always the concept?
Aren't there a lot of concepts?
I'd appreciate it if it was a thing.
Professional.
Professional and perfect are the same person I have in mind right now.
Let's go with that.
I told you I wouldn't say that.
Let's go with perfect.
Perfect.
That's good. You're getting better.
Yes, yes.
Yes. Amachan's idea of perfect.
I wonder if I can float it.
I can get it.
Perfect!
Who is it?
Keisuke Honda.
Soccer player?
He's Keisuke Honda, a soccer player and coach.
He's the first person that came to mind.
Perfect?What's perfect?
It's cool.
I mean, he's got a cool face, but...
But I thought his play was cool.
And he always says what he means.
You're a loud guy.
Like a big mouth.
And he scores every time.
He's cool.
But he's also a bit of a tease.
That's also a cute side.
In the sense that he has it all.
I think he's perfect.
I watched the commentary for the World Cup the other night.
I also watched the commentary.
7 minutes
Do you have any ambitions or aspirations?
Not that I want to be like this.
But if I became like this, it would be terrible.
I'm the one who's misunderstood because I only cut out this part of the show.
I'm praising him so much.
I'm praising him, but I'm saying it's because of him.
Look, he's saying that.
I'm embarrassed.
That's a compliment.
Subscribe to our channel!